ecampus.com 2016-04-16

# Help Desk - Privacy Policy | eCampus.com | Textbooks - Easy. Fast. Cheap!

## Our Privacy Commitment

eCampus.com is totally committed to protecting your privacy. We make every effort to assure your confidentiality and to keep your trust. The information you provide us in your account is used to process orders and to assist us in providing you with a more personalized shopping experience. eCampus.com utilizes every available technology to ensure that your confidential information remains secure.

eCampus.com holds your email address in strictest confidence. We do not sell, give away, or otherwise distribute your email address to any third party unless you have given us permission to do so.

## Collecting and Using Your Info

When you place an order, we'll ask you for your name, email address, mailing address, billing address, and credit card number with expiration date. This information allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. Occasionally, we may use your email address to deliver information regarding important functionality changes to our website, new services, and special offers that might be of interest to you. If you would rather not receive this type of information, please sign in to your eCampus.com My Account to unsubscribe from our promotional emails.

eCampus.com uses your purchasing information for the purpose of providing you a more efficient shopping experience and to make our recommendations about books and other merchandise that you may find interesting. We also monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop the content, design, and layout of the web site.

## Using "Cookies"

"Cookies" are small bits of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personal information, but they do store your settings and remember the contents of your shopping cart as you travel through the site or between visits. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies.

## Disclosing Your Info

eCampus.com considers the information you share with us to be personal and confidential. We do not sell, trade or rent any of your personal information to others. However, we may choose to release this information to trustworthy third parties at some point in the future with your permission. If you do not want us to share your personal information with third parties, please sign in to your eCampus.com My Account to unsubscribe from our promotional emails.

eCampus.com may also provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third parties, but these statistics will include no personal information. Finally, we may release the name, address and email address of sweepstakes entrants to reputable co-sponsors and to other third parties for the sole purpose of administering such sweepstakes.

If you visit eCampus.com via a co-branded site (by using a link to our site from a company we do business with), your personal information may be collected by both parties and used by each in accordance with their respective privacy policies. Your credit card information and password are not shared with co-branded businesses.

eCampus.com releases personal account information, in good faith, when such release is believed to be reasonably necessary. This includes situations in complying with the law; enforcing or applying the terms of any of our user agreements; or protecting the rights, property and safety of eCampus.com, our customers, or affected third parties.

## Securing Your Private Info

eCampus.com employs the latest version of Secure Socket Layer Technology (SSL) to encrypt your information and help insure that only you and eCampus.com ever see it. If your web browser doesn't permit a secure connection, eCampus.com will not accept your personal information including credit card numbers. Your browser should display a "padlock" or "key" icon in the lower margin of your web browser when a secure connection is made, and the URL bar at the top of your browser will typically show the website address preceded by the characters "https".

## Your Consent

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by eCampus.com. If we amend our Privacy Policy, we will immediately post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we gather, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. We suggest that you check this page on occasion to keep up with the most current policies.

## Your Password

eCampus.com suggests that you keep your password private and avoid disclosing it to any third parties. If others have access to your password, the possibility exists that your personal information could be compromised.

## Unsubscribing from Email

In accordance with federal laws, eCampus.com allows you unsubscribe from promotional emails. If you wish to unsubscribe, please sign in to your eCampus.com My Account to do so. Please be aware you will still receive transactional emails related to any order placed through eCampus.com such as order status updates and shipment confirmation emails.
